http://www.consultmcgregor.com/privacy.php

Home
Sitemap
Privacy
GO
Search Site:
Malta 08
Malta 08 (Feb)
Publication:2020 Conceptualizing Family Well-being
Research Article:2020 David Selbyâ€™s radical approach to sustainability education
Research Article:2020 Conceptualizing trans well-being with transdisciplinarity
Research Article:Transdisciplinary curriculum: Educational philosophy and rationale (2019)
McGregor Consulting Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use any personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.
Personal Information You Choose to Provide
Contact Information.
You may provide McGregor Consulting Group information about yourself, your firm or company, and your practices when you submit or complete any of our online contact forms or submission forms, or register for email newsletters and alerts.
Email Information.
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.
Web Site Use Information
Similar to other commercial web sites, our web site may utilize standard technologies such as “sessions” or "cookies" and web server logs to collect information about how our web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our web site, and the web sites visited just before and just after our web site.  We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small pieces of code called “web beacons” or “clear gifs” to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them.
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at info@consultmcgregor.com.
What Are Cookies?
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.
How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?
In some cases, we use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
McGregor Consulting Group does not share personal information with any third parties except as disclosed in this policy.
Notice of New Services and Changes
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by sending us an email request at info@consultmcgregor.com.
How Do We Protect Your Information?
Certain Disclosures
We may disclosure your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or Affiliated Parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, the Site, the users of the Site, and/or our Affiliated Parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of the Site, us, or third parties.
What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?
We are not responsible for the practices employed by web sites linked to or from our web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our web site.
Please remember that when you use a link to go from our web site to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites which have a link on our web site, is subject to that web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.
Your Consent
By using our web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
About
Research
Publications
Keynotes
Consultancy Work
Awards and Recognition
Home Economics Links
Contact
Copyright © 2020, McGregor Consulting Group. All rights reserved.
